Contact

court.m.tucker@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/courtt3d (LinkedIn) courtt3d.blogspot.com (Portfolio) ctucker9233.github.io/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills HTML5 CSS JavaScript

Certifications
Build Website Uls

Honors-Awards
Graduated with Honors

Courtney Tucker

Web Developer

El Cajon, California

Summary

Who am I? I am a person of many talents. I have studied Game Art and Design, creating many 3D assets for personal projects and for Sony Online Entertainment, now known as Daybreak Games. I have worked for years in my family business developing and maintaining our e-commerce website using the Magento 2 platform. I have followed my passion for Web Development, recently enrolling in UCSD's Coding Bootcamp. It is an intense program that covers the full stack of web development technologies. I want to take these skills into a full-fledged tech career.

I continue to follow this same passion and drive in my personal projects which are available for viewing on my portfolio site. I would enjoy hearing your feedback. If you feel my skills fit a particular position in your company, please don't hesitate to contact me.

Experience

Cash and Carry Furniture

Management Information Systems Manager

December 2018 - Present

Greater San Diego Area

My role is to the learn every aspect of the RetailVantage POS software and to teach and advise all the employees about how to properly utilize it. It is my responsibility to ensure that all standard operating procedures with the software are followed, to suggest changes current operating procedures if needed and to provide quality assurance to correct any critical mistakes. I work directly with the Head of Operations to quickly solve any problems.

Cash and Carry Furniture Sales Associate Trainee July 2016 - Present I'm currently training to become a sales associate in the retail furniture industry. I love helping customers find that perfect piece. It's like a treasure hunt. I look forward to learning the business and improving customer service.

Skills Used:

- -Customer Service
- -Multi-tasking
- -Communication
- -Problem Solving
- -Good listener
- -Fast learner

Cash and Carry Furniture Lead Web Designer/Developer May 2015 - Present

Greater San Diego Area

A recently created position in this company I am privileged to lead. As Lead Web Developer/Designer, it is my job to manage all aspects of the process from learning the Magento E-Commerce platform to collaborating with coworkers on the layout, graphics, timeline, etc. I report weekly to my senior manager on progress and respond to feedback in a positive and timely manner.

Software/Programs/Languages Used:

- -Magento Community Edition
- -Photoshop
- -FTP
- -HTML/CSS/PHP

Skills Utilized

- -Testing/Debugging
- -Graphic Design
- -Attention to Detail
- -Coding/Scripting
- -Excellent Communication
- -Critical Thinking and Problem Solving

CT Video Editing (Client: Educate For Life) Youtube Video Editor and Podcast Creator January 2016 - Present

Greater San Diego Area

I edit the Youtube videos for my client, Educate For Life, using the Screenflow software to sync up the production audio with the video and perform any other edits that my client wants. I create podcast audio that accompanies the Youtube video and it gets posted on iTunes, TuneIn, and many other podcast platforms.

Cash and Carry Furniture
Office Assistant/Data Entry Specialist/Data Analyst
January 2007 - Present

Process customer invoices and manage the filing system.

Organize and sort merchandise invoices

Receive merchandise on dock, tag all items accurately and enter items in computer

Collect data from Point of Sales System and generate accurate Sales Reports
Review computer generated reports to ensure the accuracy of data
Develop a database system to track merchandise received and merchandise
paid

CT Video Editing (Client: Educate For Life)
Powerpoint Presentation Re-designer and Video Editor
September 2014 - January 2016 (1 year 5 months)

- *Unify the Layout and Design of Multiple Power Point Presentations
- *Prepare each presentation according to a style guide
- *Upload presentations to file share system for use in online video classes
- *Edit videos of presentation and presenter for use on Udemy.com
- -Sync audio with video
- -Edit video in Screenflow to fit time requirements
- -Export and Upload videos to online platform
- -Keep all files well organized

Glacier studios Environment and Prop Artist February 2014 - September 2014 (8 months) Virtual

Involved in all aspects of creating 3D Prop and Environment Assets.

Racket Games
Artist

August 2013 - January 2014 (6 months)

Create concepts, mock-ups, and various art assets.

The Art Institute of California, A College of Argosy University Student

July 2010 - June 2013 (3 years)

Worked on various group and individual projects. Modeled, unwrapped, and textured game ready assets using 3DS Max, Maya, Zbrush, Photoshop, and UDK.

Sony Online Entertainment Internship - Environment Artist October 2012 - December 2012 (3 months)

Greater San Diego Area

Interned for the Clone Wars Adventures team where I created many assets that have been released in-game.

Education

The Art Institute of California-San Diego Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Game Art and Design · (2010 - 2013)

Additional Creative Education (2011 - 2011)

San Diego State University-California State University Computer Science · (2008 - 2010)

University of California San Diego
Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp, Web Development · (2019)